A Guide to the Correspondence and subject files of the State Coordinator of the Virginia Department of Emergency Management, 1987-2013
Library of Virginia
- Correspondence and subject files (Acc. 41597), 1987-1999.
  - Subject: Virginia Spill Response Council, 1990. (Box 15)
  - Subject: National Weather Service, 1990. (Box 15)
  - Subject: Research alternatives, 1990. (Box 15)
  - State: Local government, 1990. (Box 15)
  - State: Other state agencies, 1990. (Box 15)
  - State: Accounts, Dept. of, 1990. (Box 15)
  - State: Commission on Local Government, 1990. (Box 15)
  - State: Conservation and Historic Resources, Dept. of, 1990. (Box 15)
  - State: Emergency Management Services, Dept. of, 1990. (Box 15)
  - State: Fire Programs, Dept. of, 1990. (Box 15)
  - State: Forestry, Dept. of, 1990. (Box 15)
  - State: General Services, Dept. of, 1990. (Box 15)
  - State: Health Dept., 1990. (Box 15)
  - State: Information Technology, Dept. of, 1990. (Box 15)
  - State: Military Affairs, Dept. of, 1990. (Box 15)
  - State: Minority Business Enterprise, Dept. of, 1990. (Box 15)
  - State: Motor Vehicles, Dept. of, 1990. (Box 15)
  - State: Personnel and Training, Dept. of, 1990. (Box 15)
  - State: Planning and Budget, Dept. of, 1990. (Box 15)
  - State: Purchase and Supply, Division of, 1990. (Box 15)
  - State: State Police, 1990. (Box 15)
  - State: Transportation, Dept. of (VDOT), 1990. (Box 15)
  - State: Waste Management, Dept. of, 1990. (Box 15)
  - State: Water Control Board, State, 1990. (Box 15)
  - Federal: Agency for International Development, 1990. (Box 15)
  - Federal: Dept. of Agriculture (USDA), 1990. (Box 15)
  - Federal: Dept. of the Army, 1990. (Box 15)
  - Federal: Dept. of Energy, 1990. (Box 15)
  - Federal: Dept. of the Navy, 1990. (Box 15)
  - Federal: Environmental Protection Agency (EPA), 1990. (Box 15)
  - Federal: Federal Emergency Management Agency (FEMA), 1990 Jan-June. (Box 15)
  - Federal: Federal Emergency Management Agency (FEMA), 1990 July-Dec. (Box 15)
  - Federal: National Oceanic and Atmosperic Administration (NOAA), 1990. (Box 15)
  - Federal: Nuclear Regulatory Commission (NRC), 1990. (Box 15)
  - Federal: Small Business Administration (SBA), 1990. (Box 15)
  - Subject: Hazardous Waste Task Force, 1990. (Box 15)
  - Subject: Disaster Relief Act of 1974, 1990. (Box 15)
  - Subject: Emergency Broadcast System, 1990. (Box 15)
  - Subject: Hazardous materials, 1990. (Box 15)
  - Subject: Hazardous materials training, 1990. (Box 15)
  - Subject: Transportation of high level radioactive waste, 1990. (Box 15)
  - Subject: Search and Rescue, 1990. (Box 15)
  - State Coordinator (Addison E. Slayton, Jr.) - Chronological correspondence, 1991 Jan. (Box 16)
  - State Coordinator (Addison E. Slayton, Jr.) - Chronological correspondence, 1991 Feb. (Box 16)
  - State Coordinator (Addison E. Slayton, Jr.) - Chronological correspondence, 1991 Mar. (Box 16)
  - State Coordinator (Addison E. Slayton, Jr.) - Chronological correspondence, 1991 Apr. (Box 16)
  - State Coordinator (Addison E. Slayton, Jr.) - Chronological correspondence, 1991 May. (Box 16)
  - State Coordinator (Addison E. Slayton, Jr.) - Chronological correspondence, 1991 June. (Box 16)
  - State Coordinator (Addison E. Slayton, Jr.) - Chronological correspondence, 1991 July. (Box 16)
  - State Coordinator (Addison E. Slayton, Jr.) - Chronological correspondence, 1991 Aug. (Box 16)
  - State Coordinator (Addison E. Slayton, Jr.) - Chronological correspondence, 1991 Sept. (Box 16)
  - State Coordinator (Addison E. Slayton, Jr.) - Chronological correspondence, 1991 Oct. (Box 16)
  - State Coordinator (Addison E. Slayton, Jr.) - Chronological correspondence, 1991 Nov. (Box 16)
  - State Coordinator (Addison E. Slayton, Jr.) - Chronological correspondence, 1991 Dec. (Box 16)
  - Governor's Office: Wilder, Lawrence Douglas, 1991. (Box 16)
  - Governor's Office: Shropshire, J.T. - Chief of Staff, 1991. (Box 16)
  - Governor's Office: Haskell, Elizabeth - Secretary of Natural Resources, 1991. (Box 16)
  - Governor's Office: Davidson, Glenn - Virginia Liaison Office, 1991. (Box 16)
  - Governor's Office: Senate Finance Committee, 1991. (Box 16)
  - Governor's Office: Attorney General's Office, 1991. (Box 16)
  - Governor's Office: Secretary of the Commonwealth, 1991. (Box 16)
  - Governor's Office: Suthard, Robert L. - Secretary of Public Safety, 1991 Jan-Mar. (Box 16)
  - Governor's Office: Suthard, Robert L. - Secretary of Public Safety, 1991 Apr-June. (Box 16)
  - Governor's Office: Suthard, Robert L. - Secretary of Public Safety, 1991 July-Sept. (Box 16)
  - Governor's Office: Suthard, Robert L. - Secretary of Public Safety, 1991 Oct-Dec. (Box 16)
  - Federal: Agency for International Development, 1991. (Box 17)
  - Federal: Dept. of Agriculture (USDA), 1991. (Box 17)
  - Federal: Dept of the Army, 1991. (Box 17)
  - Federal: Dept. of Energy, 1991. (Box 17)
  - Federal: Dept. of the Navy, 1991. (Box 17)
  - Federal: Environmental Protection Agency (EPA), 1991. (Box 17)
  - Federal: Federal Emergency Management Agency (FEMA), 1991 Jan-June. (Box 17)
  - Federal: Federal Emergency Mangement Agency (FEMA), 1991 July-Dec. (Box 17)
  - Federal: National Oceanic and Atmospheric Administration (NOAA), 1991. (Box 17)
  - Federal: Nuclear Regulatory Commission (NRC), 1991. (Box 17)
  - Federal: Small Business Administration (SBA), 1991. (Box 17)
  - Federal: Dept. of Transportation- (USDOT), 1991. (Box 17)
  - State: Local government, 1991. (Box 17)
  - State: Other state agencies, 1991. (Box 17)
  - State: Accounts, Dept. of, 1991. (Box 17)
  - State: Agriculture and Consumer Services, Dept. of, 1991. (Box 17)
  - Commission on Local Government, 1991. (Box 17)
  - State: Council on the Environment, 1991. (Box 17)
  - State: Council on Information Management, 1991. (Box 17)
  - State: Fire Programs, Dept. of, 1991. (Box 17)
  - State: General Services, Dept. of, 1991. (Box 17)
  - State: Health, Dept. of, 1991. (Box 17)
  - State: Information Technology, Dept. of (DIT), 1991. (Box 17)
  - State: Joint Legislative Audit and Review Commission (JLARC), 1991. (Box 17)
  - State: Military Affairs, Dept. of, 1991. (Box 17)
  - State: Mines, Minerals and Energy, Dept. of, 1991. (Box 17)
  - State: Minority Business Enterprise, Dept. of, 1991. (Box 17)
  - State: Motor Vehicles, Dept. of, 1991. (Box 17)
  - State: Personnel and Training, Dept. of, 1991. (Box 17)
  - State: Planning and Budget, Dept. of, 1991. (Box 17)
  - State: State Library, 1991. (Box 17)
  - State: State Police, Dept. of, 1991. (Box 17)
  - State: Transportation, Dept. of (VDOT), 1991. (Box 17)
  - State: Volunteerism, Office of, 1991. (Box 17)
  - State: Waste Management, Dept. of, 1991. (Box 17)
  - State: Water Control Board, State, 1991. (Box 17)
  - Program: Local Affairs Division, 1991. (Box 17)
  - Program: Operations Division, 1991. (Box 17)
  - Program: Plans Division, 1991. (Box 17)
  - Program: Program Development, Evaluation and Training Division, 1991. (Box 17)
  - Program: Public Assistance Division, 1991. (Box 17)
  - Program: Public Information Division, 1991. (Box 17)
  - Program: Special Programs Division, 1991. (Box 17)
  - Program: Support Division, 1991. (Box 17)
  - Program: Technological Hazards Branch, 1991. (Box 17)
  - Subject: Civil Air Patrol, 1991. (Box 18)
  - Subject: Civil Defense, 1991. (Box 18)
  - Subject: Comprehensive Cooperative Agreement (CCA), 1991. (Box 18)
  - Subject: Emergency Broadcast Systems, 1991. (Box 18)
  - Subject: Emergency Management, 1991. (Box 18)
  - Subject: Emergency Medical Services Advisory Board, 1991. (Box 18)
  - Subject: Emergency Management training, 1991. (Box 18)
  - Subject: Energy Emergency - Fuel, 1990-1991. (Box 18)
  - Subject: Hazardous materials, 1991. (Box 18)
  - Subject: Hazardous materials - Training, 1991. (Box 18)
  - Subject: National Emergency Management Association (NEMA), 1991 Jan-June. (Box 18)
  - Subject: National Emergency Management Association (NEMA), 1991 July-Dec. (Box 18)
  - Subject: National Weather Service, 1991. (Box 18)
  - Subject: North Anna, 1991. (Box 18)
  - Subject: Project Streamline Interagency Task Force, 1991. (Box 18)
  - Subject: Radiological Emergency Response Plans, 1991. (Box 18)
  - Subject: Research alternatives, 1991. (Box 18)
  - Subject: Search and Rescue, 1991. (Box 18)
  - Subject: Sole Source purchases, 1991. (Box 18)
  - Subject: State-wide Interdepartmental Radio System (SIRS) Advisory Board, 1991. (Box 18)
  - Subject: Study of Hepatitis B - Immunization requirement, 1991. (Box 18)
  - Subject: SARA (Superfund), 1991. (Box 18)
  - Subject: Virginia Emergency Response Council, 1991. (Box 18)
  - Subject: Surry Power Plant, 1991. (Box 18)
  - Subject: Virginia National Guard, 1991. (Box 18)
  - Subject: Virginia Petroleum Council, 1991. (Box 18)
  - Subject: Virginia Power, 1991. (Box 18)
  - State Coordinator (Addison E. Slayton, Jr.) - Chronological correspondence, 1992 Jan. (Box 19)
  - State Coordinator (Addison E. Slayton, Jr.) - Chronological correspondence, 1992 Feb. (Box 19)
  - State Coordinator (Addison E. Slayton, Jr.) - Chronological correspondence, 1992 Mar. (Box 19)
  - State Coordinator (Addison E. Slayton, Jr.) - Chronological correspondence, 1992 Apr. (Box 19)
  - State Coordinator (Addison E. Slayton, Jr.) - Chronological correspondence, 1992 May. (Box 19)
  - State Coordinator (Addison E. Slayton, Jr.) - Chronological correspondence, 1992 June. (Box 19)
  - State Coordinator (Addison E. Slayton, Jr.) - Chronological correspondence, 1992 July. (Box 19)
  - State Coordinator (Addison E. Slayton, Jr.) - Chronological correspondence, 1992 Aug. (Box 19)
  - State Coordinator (Addison E. Slayton, Jr.) - Chronological correspondence, 1992 Sept. (Box 19)
  - State Coordinator (Addison E. Slayton, Jr.) - Chronological correspondence, 1992 Oct. (Box 19)
  - State Coordinator (Addison E. Slayton, Jr.) - Chronological correspondence, 1992 Nov. (Box 19)
  - State Coordinator (Addison E. Slayton, Jr.) - Chronological correspondence, 1992 Dec. (Box 19)
  - Program: Campbell, Stan - Integrated Flood Observing and Warning System (IFLOWS), 1992. (Box 19)
  - Program: Local Affairs Division, 1992. (Box 19)
  - Program: Operations Division, 1992. (Box 19)
  - Program: Plans Division, 1992. (Box 19)
  - Program: Program Development, Evaluation and Training Division, 1992. (Box 19)
  - PublicProgram: Assistance Division, 1992. (Box 19)
  - Program: Public Information Division, 1992. (Box 19)
  - Program: Support Division, 1992. (Box 19)
  - Program: Technological Hazards Branch, 1992. (Box 19)
  - Governor's Office: Rollins, O. Randolph - Secretary of Public Safety, 1992 Jan-Mar. (Box 20)
  - Governor's Office: Rollins, O. Randolph - Secretary of Public Safety, 1992 Apr-June. (Box 20)
  - Governor's Office: Rollins, O. Randolph - Secretary of Public Safety, 1992 July-Sept. (Box 20)
  - Governor's Office: Rollins, O. Randolph - Secretary of Public Safety, 1992 Oct-Dec. (Box 20)
  - Governor's Office:: Virginia Liaison Office, 1992. (Box 20)
  - Governor's Office:: Attorney General, 1992. (Box 20)
  - State: Accounts, Dept. of, 1992. (Box 20)
  - State: Code Commission, 1992. (Box 20)
  - State: Conservation and Recreation, Dept. of, 1992. (Box 20)
  - State: Council on the Environment, 1992. (Box 20)
  - State: Council on Information Management, 1992. (Box 20)
  - State: Emergency Medical Services, Dept. of, 1992. (Box 20)
  - State: Fire Programs, Dept. of, 1992. (Box 20)
  - State: Forestry, Dept. of, 1992. (Box 20)
  - State: General Services, Dept. of, 1992. (Box 20)
  - State: Health Dept., 1992. (Box 20)
  - State: Information Technology, Dept. of, 1992. (Box 20)
  - State: Legislative Services, Division of, 1992. (Box 20)
  - State: Mental Health and Mental Retardation, Dept. of, 1992. (Box 20)
  - State: Military Affairs, Dept. of, 1992. (Box 20)
  - State: Motor Vehicles, Dept. of, 1992. (Box 20)
  - State: Personnel and Training, Dept. of, 1992. (Box 20)
  - State: Planning and Budget, Dept. of, 1992. (Box 20)
  - State: State Library, 1992. (Box 20)
  - State: State Police, Dept. of, 1992. (Box 20)
  - State: Volunteerism, Office of, 1992. (Box 20)
  - State: Waste Management, Dept. of, 1992. (Box 20)
  - State: Water Control Board, 1992. (Box 20)
  - Federal: Dept. of the Army, 1992. (Box 20)
  - Federal: Environmental Protection Agency (EPA), 1992. (Box 20)
  - Federal: Federal Emergency Management Agency (FEMA), 1992 Jan-June. (Box 20)
  - Federal: Federal Emergency Management Agency (FEMA), 1992 July-Dec. (Box 20)
  - Federal: National Oceanic and Atmospheric Administration (NOAA), 1992. (Box 20)
  - Federal: Nuclear Regulatory Commission (NRC), 1992. (Box 20)
  - Federal: Small Business Administration (SBA), 1992. (Box 20)
  - Federal: Dept. of Transportation (USDOT), 1992. (Box 20)
  - Subject: Blanket Campaign, 1992. (Box 21)
  - Subject: Civil Air Patrol, 1992. (Box 21)
  - Subject: Comprehensive Cooperative Agreement (CCA), 1992. (Box 21)
  - Subject: Emergency Broadcast System, 1992. (Box 21)
  - Subject: Hazardous Materials Transportation Uniform Safety Act, 1991-1992. (Box 21)
  - Subject: Study of Transporation of Hazardous Materials in Virginia (SJR 155), 1992. (Box 21)
  - Subject: Study of Transportation Policy (SJR 30), 1990. (Box 21)
  - Subject: Hazard mitigation, 1992. (Box 21)
  - Subject: IFLOWS, 1992. (Box 21)
  - Subject: Individual and Family Grant Program, 1992. (Box 21)
  - Subject: National Emergency Management Association (NEMA), 1992. (Box 21)
  - Subject: National Governors Association (NGA), 1992. (Box 21)
  - Subject: National Weather Service, 1992. (Box 21)
  - Subject: North Anna, 1992. (Box 21)
  - Subject: Project Streamline Interagency Task Force, 1992. (Box 21)
  - Subject: Radiological Emergency Response Plan, 1992. (Box 21)
  - Subject: Response Team (National and Federal), 1992. (Box 21)
  - Subject: Relief of landowners from liability resulting from illegal dumping of hazardous materials (SJR 202), 1992. (Box 21)
  - Subject: Sole Source Purchases, 1992. (Box 21)
  - Subject: Spent Nuclear Fuel, 1992. (Box 21)
  - Subject: Surry Power Plant, 1992. (Box 21)
  - Subject: Telecommunication Services, 1992. (Box 21)
  - Subject: Virginia National Guard, 1992. (Box 21)
  - Subject: Virginia Power, 1992. (Box 21)
  - State Coordinator (Addison E. Slayton, Jr.) - Chronological correspondence, 1993 Jan. (Box 22)
  - State Coordinator (Addison E. Slayton, Jr.) - Chronological correspondence, 1993 Feb. (Box 22)
  - State Coordinator (Addison E. Slayton, Jr.) - Chronological correspondence, 1993 Mar. (Box 22)
  - State Coordinator (Addison E. Slayton, Jr.) - Chronological correspondence, 1993 Apr. (Box 22)
  - State Coordinator (Addison E. Slayton, Jr.) - Chronological correspondence, 1993 May. (Box 22)
  - State Coordinator (Addison E. Slayton, Jr.) - Chronological correspondence, 1993 June. (Box 22)
  - State Coordinator (Addison E. Slayton, Jr.) - Chronological correspondence, 1993 July. (Box 22)
  - State Coordinator (Addison E. Slayton, Jr.) - Chronological correspondence, 1993 Aug. (Box 22)
  - State Coordinator (Addison E. Slayton, Jr.) - Chronological correspondence, 1993 Sept. (Box 22)
  - State Coordinator (Addison E. Slayton, Jr.) - Chronological correspondence, 1993 Oct. (Box 22)
  - State Coordinator (Addison E. Slayton, Jr.) - Chronological correspondence, 1993 Sept. (Box 22)
  - State Coordinator (Addison E. Slayton, Jr.) - Chronological correspondence, 1993 Oct. (Box 22)
  - State Coordinator (Addison E. Slayton, Jr.) - Chronological correspondence, 1993 Nov. (Box 22)
  - State Coordinator (Addison E. Slayton, Jr.) - Chronological correspondence, 1993 Dec. (Box 22)
  - Program: Cambell, Stan - Integrated Flood Observing and Warning System (IFLOWS), 1993. (Box 22)
  - Program: Grants Administration Division, 1993. (Box 22)
  - Program: Operations Division, 1993. (Box 22)
  - Program: Plans Division, 1993. (Box 22)
  - Program: Public Assistance Division, 1993. (Box 22)
  - Program: Public Information Division, 1993. (Box 22)
  - Program: Regional Coordinators, 1993. (Box 22)
  - Program: RIMC Division, 1993. (Box 22)
  - Program: Special Programs Division, 1993. (Box 22)
  - Program: Support Division, 1993. (Box 22)
  - Program: Technological Hazards Branch, 1993. (Box 22)
  - Governor's Office: Wilder, L. Douglas, 1993. (Box 23)
  - Governor's Office: Secretary of Public Safety, 1993 Jan-Mar. (Box 23)
  - Governor's Office: Secretary of Public Safety, 1993 Apr-June. (Box 23)
  - Governor's Office: Secretary of Public Safety, 1993 July-Sept. (Box 23)
  - Governor's Office: Secretary of Public Safety, 1993 Oct-Dec. (Box 23)
  - Governor's Office: Attorney General, 1993. (Box 23)
  - Governor's Office: Virginia Liaison Office, 1993. (Box 23)
  - Governor's Office: Senate Finance Committee, 1993. (Box 23)
  - State: Accounts, Dept. of, 1993. (Box 23)
  - State: Agriculture and Consumer Services, Dept. of, 1993. (Box 23)
  - State: Code Commission, Virginia, 1993. (Box 23)
  - State: Commission on Local Government, 1993. (Box 23)
  - State: Council of Information Management, 1993. (Box 23)
  - State: Emergency Management Services, Dept. of, 1993. (Box 23)
  - State: Employee Relations Counselors, Dept. of, 1993. (Box 23)
  - State: Environmental Quality, Dept. of, 1993. (Box 23)
  - State: Forestry, Dept. of, 1993. (Box 23)
  - State: General Services, Dept. of, 1993. (Box 23)
  - State: Information Technology, Dept. of, 1993. (Box 23)
  - State: Joint Legislative Audit and Review Commission, 1993. (Box 23)
  - State: Military Affairs, Dept. of, 1993. (Box 23)
  - State: Mines, Minerals and Energy, Dept. of, 1993. (Box 23)
  - State: Minority Business Enterprise, Dept. of, 1993. (Box 23)
  - State: Motor Vehicles, Dept. of, 1993. (Box 23)
  - State: Personnel and Training, Dept. of, 1993. (Box 23)
  - State: Planning and Budget, Dept. of, 1993. (Box 23)
  - State: State Library, 1993. (Box 23)
  - State: State Police, Dept. of, 1993. (Box 23)
  - State: Transportation, Dept. of, 1993. (Box 23)
  - State: Volunteerism, Office of, 1993. (Box 23)
  - Federal: Agriculture, Dept. of (USDA), 1993. (Box 24)
  - Federal: Army, Dept. of the, 1993. (Box 24)
  - Federal: Navy, Dept. of the, 1993. (Box 24)
  - Federal: Energy, Dept. of, 1993. (Box 24)
  - Federal: Environmental Protection Agecy (EPA), 1993. (Box 24)
  - Federal: Federal Emergency Management Agency (FEMA), 1993 Jan-Apr. (Box 24)
  - Federal: Federal Emergency Management Agency (FEMA), 1993 May-Aug. (Box 24)
  - Federal: Federal Emergency Management Agency (FEMA), 1993 Sept-Dec. (Box 24)
  - Federal: National Oceanic and Atmospheric Administration (NOAA), 1993. (Box 24)
  - Federal: Small Business Administration (SBA), 1993. (Box 24)
  - Federal: Transportation, Dept. of (USDOT), 1993. (Box 24)
  - Subject: American Red Cross, 1993. (Box 24)
  - Subject: Flood Control Advisory Commission, 1993. (Box 24)
  - Subject: Boy Scout Jamboree, 1993. (Box 24)
  - Subject: Comprehensive Cooperative Agreement (CCA), 1993. (Box 24)
  - Subject: Emergency management, 1993. (Box 24)
  - Subject: Hazard materials, 1993. (Box 24)
  - Subject: Hazardous materials - Transportation, 1993. (Box 24)
  - Subject: Hazard mitigation, 1993. (Box 24)
  - Subject: Integrated Flood Observing and Warning System (IFLOWS), 1993. (Box 24)
  - Subject: National Emergency Management Association (NEMA), 1993. (Box 24)
  - Subject: NEMA - Training and Education Committee, 1993. (Box 24)
  - Subject: National Business and Industry Advisory Council of the EBS, 1993. (Box 24)
  - Subject: National Task Force on Hazardous Materials Emergency Preparedness, 1993. (Box 24)
  - Subject: National Weather Service, 1993. (Box 24)
  - Subject: North Anna, 1993. (Box 24)
  - Subject: Radiation Advisory Board, 1993. (Box 24)
  - Subject: Radiological Emergency Response Plan, 1993. (Box 24)
  - Subject: Regional Interagency Steering Committee (RISC), 1993. (Box 25)
  - Subject: RISC - Response Program, 1993. (Box 25)
  - Subject: Search and Rescue, 1993. (Box 25)
  - Subject: Search and Rescue, Urban, 1993. (Box 25)
  - Subject: Search and Rescue, Urban - Development material, 1993. (Box 25)
  - Subject: Spent Nuclear Fuel, 1993. (Box 25)
  - Subject: Spent Nuclear Fuel - Defueled Reactor Plants, 1993. (Box 25)
  - Subject: Spent Nuclear Fuel - Foreign, 1993. (Box 25)
  - Subject: Spent Nuclear Fuel - Navy, 1993. (Box 25)
  - Subject: Southern Governors Association / Southern Regional Emergency Assistance Compact, 1993. (Box 25)
  - Subject: Spill Prevention and Response Readiness Committee, 1993. (Box 25)
  - Subject: Stafford Act, 1993. (Box 25)
  - Subject: Survivable Crisis Management, 1993. (Box 25)
  - Subject: Surry Power Plant, 1993. (Box 25)
  - Subject: Telecommunications Services, 1993. (Box 25)
  - Subject: Toxic Substance Advisory Board, 1993. (Box 25)
  - Subject: Virginia National Guard, 1993. (Box 25)
  - Subject: Virginia Power, 1993. (Box 25)
  - State Coordinator (Addison E. Slayton, Jr.) - Chronological correspondence, 1994 Jan. (Box 26)
  - State Coordinator (Addison E. Slayton, Jr.) - Chronological correspondence, 1994 Feb. (Box 26)
  - State Coordinator (Addison E. Slayton, Jr.) - Chronological correspondence, 1994 Mar. (Box 26)
  - State Coordinator (Addison E. Slayton, Jr.) - Chronological correspondence, 1994 Apr. (Box 26)
  - State Coordinator (Addison E. Slayton, Jr.) - Chronological correspondence, 1994 May. (Box 26)
  - State Coordinator (Addison E. Slayton, Jr.) - Chronological correspondence, 1994 June. (Box 26)
  - State Coordinator (Addison E. Slayton, Jr.) - Chronological correspondence, 1994 July. (Box 26)
  - State Coordinator (Addison E. Slayton, Jr.) - Chronological correspondence, 1994 Aug. (Box 26)
  - State Coordinator (Addison E. Slayton, Jr.) - Chronological correspondence, 1994 Sept. (Box 26)
  - State Coordinator (Addison E. Slayton, Jr.) - Chronological correspondence, 1994 Oct. (Box 26)
  - State Coordinator (Addison E. Slayton, Jr.) - Chronological correspondence, 1994 Nov. (Box 26)
  - State Coordinator (Addison E. Slayton, Jr.) - Chronological correspondence, 1994 Dec. (Box 26)
  - Program: Campbell, Stan - Integrated Flood Observing and Warning System (IFLOWS), 1994. (Box 26)
  - Program: Grant Administration Division, 1994. (Box 26)
  - Program: Operations Division, 1994. (Box 26)
  - Program: Plans Division, 1994. (Box 26)
  - Program: Public Information Division, 1994. (Box 26)
  - Program: Support Division, 1994. (Box 26)
  - Program: Technological Hazards Division, 1994. (Box 26)
  - Governor's Office: Secretary of the Commonwealth (Betsy Beamer), 1994. (Box 27)
  - Governor's Office: Secretary of Public Safety (Jerry Kilgore), 1994 Jan-Mar. (Box 27)
  - Governor's Office: Secretary of Public Safety (Jerry Kilgore), 1994 Apr-June. (Box 27)
  - Governor's Office: Secretary of Public Safety (Jerry Kilgore), 1994 July-Sept. (Box 27)
  - Governor's Office: Secretary of Public Safety (Jerry Kilgore), 1994 Oct-Dec. (Box 27)
  - Governor's Office: Virginia Liaison Office, 1994. (Box 27)
  - Governor's Office: House Appropriations Committee, 1994. (Box 27)
  - State: Agriculture and Consumer Services, Dept. of, 1994. (Box 27)
  - State: Accounts, Dept. of, 1994. (Box 27)
  - State: Commission on Local Government, 1994. (Box 27)
  - State: Conservation and Historic Resources, Dept. of, 1994. (Box 27)
  - State: Council on Information Management, 1994. (Box 27)
  - State: Criminal Justice Services, Dept. of, 1994. (Box 27)
  - State: Emergency Medical Services, Dept. of, 1994. (Box 27)
  - State: Employee Relations Counselors, Dept. of, 1994. (Box 27)
  - State: Environmental Quality, Dept. of, 1994. (Box 27)
  - State: Fire Programs, Dept. of, 1994. (Box 27)
  - State: Forestry, Dept. of, 1994. (Box 27)
  - State: General Services, Dept. of, 1994. (Box 27)